RISM Collections at New York University Conferences Guide to the Records of New Perspectives on Caribbean Studies: Toward the 21st Century and Prospects for Caribbean Basin Integration (Conference held at Hunter College, CUNY, August 28-September 1, 1984) RISM.RG.16.(j)
New York University Archives
- Series XVI. Audio and Video Recordings, August 1984 - March 1985, 141354
  - Audio Tapes, 141410
    - "Nationalism, Independence and Creative Florescence," Tape 2, Side A: George Lamming (cont.) (000 - 154), Rex Nettleford (166- end); Side B: Frank E. Manning (500 - 715), Gordon Rohlehr (723 - end), undated; 141433 (Box 25, Cassette 9)
    - "'Nationalism, Independence and Creative Florescence,' Tape 3," Side A: Gordon Rohlehr (000 - 230), Errol Hill (245 - ), undated; 141432 (Box 25, Cassette 10)
    - "'Process of Ethnicity,' Aug 30, Tape 1," Aug 30, Tape 1," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141431 (Box 25, Cassette 11)
    - "'Process of Ethnicity,' Aug 30, Tape 2," Aug 30, Tape 1," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141430 (Box 25, Cassette 12)
    - "'Process of Ethnicity,' Aug 30, Tape 1," Aug 30, Tape 1," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141429 (Box 25, Cassette 13)
    - "'Health in the Caribbean and Central America,'" Aug 31, Tape 1," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141428 (Box 25, Cassette 14)
    - "'Health in the Caribbean and Central America,' Aug 31, Tape 2," Side A: Peter Carr; Side B: no listing, undated; 141427 (Box 25, Cassette 15)
    - "'Health in the Caribbean and Central America," Aug 31, Tape 3, first part of Side A: no listing (000 - 204) "Regional and International Migration" (205 - end), Saskia Sassen-Koob, Linda Basch; Side B: Linda Basch (cont.), Michel S. Laguerre, Jack Harewood, undated; 141426 (Box 25, Cassette 16)
    - "'Public Health Indices of Development,' Tape 1, Side A: no listing; Side B: "Regional and International Migration," Michel S. Laguerre "(intra-Haitian migration)", undated; 141425 (Box 25, Cassette 17)
    - "Regional and International Migration," Aug 31, Tape 2," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141424 (Box 25, Cassette 18)
    - "'Regional and International Migration,' Aug 31, Tape 3," Sides A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141423 (Box 25, Cassette 19)
    - "Political Economy and Sociocultural Change," Aug 31, Tape 1, Side A: Roy Brice-Laporte, Peter D. Phillips (427 - ); Side B: Peter D. Phillips (cont.) (000 - 274), Jose Moreno (274 - end), undated; 141422 (Box 25, Cassette 20)
    - "Political Economy and Sociocultural Change," Aug 31, Tape 2, Side A: Jose Moreno (000 - 032), Hilbourne A. Watson (032 - 443), Gérard Pierre-Charles (473 - end); Side B: Gérard Pierre-Charles (cont.) (000 - end), undated; 141421 (Box 25, Cassette 21)
    - "Political Economy and Sociocultural Change," Aug 31, Tape 3, Side A: Locksley Edmondson (000 - 290), Kenneth Erickson (292 - 401), Eddie Greene (410 - 516), Open discussion; Side B: Open Discussion (cont.), 1992; 141420 (Box 25, Cassette 22)
    - "Agriculture and New Technologies: Dependency and Self- Reliance," Tape 1, Side A: Aaron Segal, Trevor M. A. Farrell; Side B: Trevor M. A. Farrell (cont.), Verne W. Loose, Lawrence A. Wilson, undated; 141419 (Box 25, Cassette 23)
    - "Agriculture and New Technologies: Dependency and Self-Reliance," Tape 2, Side A: Gerald F. Murray, undated; 141418 (Box 25, Cassette 24)
    - "'Political Economy of the Caribbean Basin Integration,' Sept 1, Tape 1," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141417 (Box 25, Cassette 25)
    - "Political Economy of the Caribbean Basin Integration," Sept 1, Tape 2," Side A: no listing; Side B: no listing, undated; 141416 (Box 25, Cassette 26)
    - "'Caribbean Basin: Crisis, Reaction and Response,' Sept 1, Tape 1," Side A: "A.M. sesson"; Side B: C. Y. Thomas, Leslie Lett, undated; 141415 (Box 25, Cassette 27)
    - "'Caribbean Basin: Crisis, Reaction and Response,' Sept 1, Tape 2," Side A: Archie Singham, Dessima Williams; Side B: Dessima Williams (cont.), Lucille Mair, Jay R. Mandle, Rickey Singh, undated; 141414 (Box 25, Cassette 28)
    - "'Caribbean Basin: Crisis, Reaction and Response,' Sept 1, Tape 3," Side A: Jorge Sol, Michael Manley; Side B: Michael Manley (cont.), Award Ceremony, undated; 141413 (Box 25, Cassette 29)
    - "'Caribbean Basin: Crisis, Reaction and Response," Sept 1, Tape 4," Side A: "Award Ceremony"; Side B: no listing, undated; 141412 (Box 25, Cassette 30)
    - "Caribbean Tapes Sample Rough" (audio) sample transfer, undated; 141411 (Box 25, Cassette 31)
  - Video Tape Shelf List, 141383
    - "Caribbean Tapes Selects I" [missing], undated; 141409 (Box 26, Reel 68768/1)
    - "Caribbean Basin: Crisis Reaction and Response, Playhouse (live) Session, Clive Thomas [C. Y. Thomas], Roy Neehall, Archie Singham, Roll 1 (complete)", undated; 141408 (Box 26, Reel 68768/2)
    - "Caribbean Tapes Selects II", undated; 141407 (Box 26, Reel 68768/3)
    - "Session I. (25 min.) Symbolic Expressions in Politics (cont.) Original, Tape 2, Camera 1" [Haitian Interview], undated; 141406 (Box 26, Reel 68768/4)
    - "Caribbean Conflict and Response, Original, Tape 6A, Camera 2", undated; 141405 (Box 26, Reel 68768/5)
    - "Caribbean Conflict and Response (cont.), Original, Tape 6, Camera 1", undated; 141404 (Box 26, Reel 68768/6)
    - "Session I. Symbolic Expressions in Politics, Original, Tape 1A, Camera 2", undated; 141403 (Box 26, Reel 68768/7)
    - "Session I. Symbolic Expressions in Politics, (cont.) Original, Tape 2A, Camera 2" [Haitian Interview], undated; 141402 (Box 26, Reel 68768/8)
    - "Caribbean Oil, Original, Tape 7, Single Camera", undated; 141401 (Box 26, Reel 68768/9)
    - Untitled, undated; 141400 (Box 26, Reel 68768/10)
    - "The Caribbean Today: Obstacles to Change, Camera 1", undated; 141399 (Box 26, Reel 68768/11)
    - "The Caribbean Today: Obstacles to Change, Camera 2", undated; 141398 (Box 26, Reel 68768/12)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Caribbean Crisis, Saturday afternoon, Live Session, Roll One: Clive Thomas [C. Y. Thomas], Roy Neehall, Archie Singham, undated; 141397 (Box 26, Reel 68768/13)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Caribbean Crisis, Saturday afternoon, Live Session, Roll One, Clive Thomas [C. Y. Thomas], Roy Neehall, Archie Singham; Playhouse Session, Roll 2, Camera 1", undated; 141396 (Box 27, Reel 68768/14)
    - "Caribbean Conference, 'Caribbean Crisis,' Saturday afternoon, Live Session, Camera 1, Tape 3", undated; 141395 (Box 27, Reel 68768/15)
    - "End of Manley's [Micheael Manley] Speech, Awards and speech by George Lamming," Tape 4 (end of playhouse [session])", undated; 141394 (Box 27, Reel 68768/16)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Saturday, Live Session, panelists, audience, Dessima Williams, undated; 141393 (Box 27, Reel 68768/17)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Saturday, Live Session, Manley [Michael Manley], Camera 2, Roll 3, (000-782)", undated; 141392 (Box 27, Reel 68768/18)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Playhouse Session, Michael Manley, Camera 3, Tape 2 (from the balcony)", undated; 141391 (Box 27, Reel 68768/19)
    - "Caribbean Conference, Playhouse Session Awards, includes Lamming [George Lamming] Speech contained in Tape 4, Camera 1", undated; 141390 (Box 27, Reel 68768/20)
    - "Original Tape 4A, Camera 1, 25 min.", undated; 141389 (Box 27, Reel 68768/21)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 4, Camera 2, 25 min.", undated; 141388 (Box 27, Reel 68768/22)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 5, Camera 1, 39 min., Beginning of Caribbean Crisis and Response", undated; 141387 (Box 27, Reel 68768/23)
    - "Migration (cont.) Historical Overview, Original, Tape 5A, Camera 2, 39 min.; beginning of "Caribbean Crisis and Response", undated; 141386 (Box 27, Reel 68768/24)
    - "Haitian Interview (cont.), Original, Tape 3, Camera 1, Migration", undated; 141385 (Box 27, Reel 68768/25)
    - "Haiti (1st part), Migration (1st part), Original, Tape 3A, Camera 2", undated; 141384 (Box 27, Reel 68768/26)
  - Digibeta versions of tapes 1-26 and DVDs 1-26, 141355 (Box 29)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 1, 141382 (Box 28, Reel 1)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 2, 141381 (Box 28, Reel 2)
    - Rism Digibeta tape 3, 141380 (Box 28, Reel 3)
    - Rism digibeta tape 4, 141379 (Box 28, Reel 4)
    - Rism digibeta tape 5, 141378 (Box 28, Reel 5)
    - Rism digibeta tape 6, 141377 (Box 28, Reel 6)
    - Rism digibeta tape 7, 141376 (Box 28, Reel 7)
    - Rism digibeta tape 8, 141375 (Box 28, Reel 8)
    - Rism digibeta tape 9, 141374 (Box 28, Reel 9)
    - Rism digibeta tape 10, 141373 (Box 28, Reel 10)
    - Rism digibeta tape 11, 141372 (Box 28, Reel 11)
    - Rism digibeta tape 12, 141371 (Box 28, Reel 12)
    - Rism digibeta tape 13, 141370 (Box 28, Reel 13)
    - Rism digibeta tape 14, 141369 (Box 28, Reel 14)
    - Rism digibeta tape 15, 141368 (Box 28, Reel 15)
    - Rism digibeta tape 16, 141367 (Box 28, Reel 16)
    - Rism digibeta tape 17, 141366 (Box 29, Reel 17)
    - Rism digibeta tape 18, 141365 (Box 29, Reel 18)
    - Rism digibeta tape 19, 141364 (Box 29, Reel 19)
    - Rism digibeta tape 20, 141363 (Box 29, Reel 20)
    - Rism digibeta tape 21, 141362 (Box 29, Reel 21)
    - Rism digibeta tape 22, 141361 (Box 29, Reel 22)
    - Rism digibeta tape 23, 141360 (Box 29, Reel 23)
    - Rism digibeta tape 24, 141359 (Box 29, Reel 24)
    - Rism digibeta tape 25, 141358 (Box 29, Reel 25)
    - Rism digibeta tape 26, 141357 (Box 29, Reel 26)
- Appendix, 171281
  - Presented Papers, 1984; 171282; 1 boxes Duplicate papers as presented at the Conference (Box 30)